# Eihab Obeidat

Obeidateihab9@gmail.com (+962) 79 154 1142 Github
Portofolio
programming languages:
Javascript, C#, Python, C++,
Bash, JSX, HTML, CSS,
TypeScript, SQI

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Full stack developer, Freelance

March 2021 to current

- Designed and developed web applications.
- Integrated security measures.
- Designed database structures.
- Managed site functionality & implemented application features.

# Cyber security engineer, PTTCT

Aug 2019 to Dec 2020

- Implemented penetration testing and vulnerability assessment projects.
- Maintained office servers, computers, printers, cables and other.
- Implemented pearson VUE authorized Test Center.
- customized backdoors, bruteforce, Web Applications automation tools.

# Technical support engineer, ESTARTA

Aug 2018 to Aug 2019

- Troubleshooted voice gateways and unified communication solutions.
- Designed and tested VoIP systems.
- Implemented cisco collaboration technologies.
- · Researched VoIP Protocols.

### Trainee, KADDB

May 2018 to Aug 2018

- Performed penetration testing.
- Cyber security researches.
- Simulated cyber-attack to evaluate systems.
- · customized bach scripts.

#### SKILLS

### Frameworks:

- Back-End:
  - Asp.net core
  - NodeJS
  - Flask
- Front-End:
  - ReactJS
  - Angular
- Other:
  - Arduino

#### DBMS:

- Oracle
- PostgreSQL

### **Additional**

- Agile methodology scrum master
- Git
- PL/SQL
- Bootstrap
- Other

Smart House 2021

Convert any facility to a smart one in a very simple, cheap and effective way.

### Penetration testing projects

2020

participated in several penetration testing and vulnerability assessment projects for government agencies.

Smart Brain 9

Face detection web application using clarifai AI models, deployed on heroku. react.js used in front-end and node.js, express.js connected by Kenx to the postgreSQL database back-end.

# Wireless gesture control robot

2018

A way for helping disabled people, by making movements by hand gesture.

#### **EDUCATION**

Jordan University of Science and Technology

2013 to 2018

Bachelor's degree in Networks Engineering and Security

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Four years of experience in information technology. Passionate about software development and engineering. Fast learner with excellent time management and decision-making abilities. Quickly adapts to new technologies and responds to challenges with determination and focus.

#### Courses:

- Complete Ethical Hacker ZTM
- CompTIA SECURITY +
- CompTIA Network +
- CCNA
- Complete Python Developer ZTM
- ISO 27001 Lead Implementer